http://www.hellenism.net/privacy-policy/

Hit enter to search or ESC to close
Disclaimer Disclaimer and Privacy informationHellenism.Net takes our visitors' privacy seriously.Some of the content used in this site was collected and sent to us over the years by various people while surfing the Internet. Since all of this content was available on the net at educational sites and had no copy-restrictions, we have assumed that the texts were allowed for re-copy for educational and non-commercial use. If this is not the case, and we are notified, we shall remove any copyrighted material immediately. Hellenism.Net offers all these articles free of charge for educational, enjoyment and reference purposes.Invitation: Many readers of these pages have published (or written) articles, articles which deserve to be read by a greater audience. We will be more than happy to place copies of any relevant article or book extract on Hellenism.Net.PRIVACY STATEMENT FOR HELLENISM.NETHellenism.Net has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Hellenism.NetIP address
We store your IP address (which doesn’t reveal anything personal about you) in logs for security reasons and statistics. By checking your IP address we can see from what country you accessed the website, for example.Cookies
Cookies are files stored on your computer with information about websites you have visited. We store a cookie named ‘Hellenism’ on your computer if you are a registered member of the Hellenism.Net forum. This eases your login process because you don’t have to login every time you visit this website. The cookie doesn’t store any personal information.AdvertisersGoogle Ads
Google uses cookies to help serve the ads it displays on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying Google ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a Google partner’s website, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser.Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website or other websites.Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Ads SettingsYou can opt out of some third-party vendors’ uses of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting www.aboutads.infoYou can also visit the Google website for the complete Google ad and content network privacy policy.Personal Information
When you register with Hellenism.Net (Forum or Personal Ads) you must enter your nickname and other optional information. This information is only made public on this website, and it is not sold or disclosed to any third party. When you post something on the forum, your nickname will be used to represent the author of that article. We don’t sell your email address. Your email address is kept in our database when you register for contact information. It is made public only on our website and only if you agree for others to contact you.External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Hellenism.Net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.Security
This website has security measures meant to prevent loss or alteration of the information. Although we can’t guaranty that the information you posted will not be altered or deleted from our website. Backups are usually made weekly.What rights you have over your dataWe do not store any personal data on this website. Please check our forum’s privacy policy for data information regarding the forum.Your consent
By using our website you understand and agree with the information displayed above.Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us hereFeatured famous GreeksLee, Tommy May 6, 2019 Socrates May 14, 2019Wilson, Rita May 16, 2019Famous GreeksActors/Actresses
Architects
Athletes
Business people
Chefs
Clothes designers
Comedians
Composers
Conductors
Get Involved
Privacy Policy© 2020 Hellenism.Net.
All Rights Reserved. Website by Esquared.
HomeAll about GreeceFacts and InformationFamous GreeksFamous Greeks (Alphabetical listing)Famous Greeks – QuizInterviews with famous GreeksAngelique RockasAngelo TsarouchasDiamanda GalasGrace JamesMario FrangoulisStratos TzortzoglouGreek culturePeople & traditionsChristmas holiday traditionsClean Monday traditionsAssumption of the Virgin MaryOctober 28th – The Ohi Day celebrationGreek languageThe Greek omogeniaGreek historyAncient GreeceByzantine periodOttoman occupationModern GreeceGreek mythologyThe age of godsThe age of mythsAphrodite and AnchisesDemeter, Persephone, and HadesDemeter and TriptolemusPentheus and DionysusPrometheus, Epimetheus and PandoraThe age of heroesAchillesAgamemnonHeraclesJason and the ArgonautsOdysseusAncient Greek literatureAesop’s fables and anecdotesAncient Greek historiansAncient Greek philosophyAncient Greek poetryComedy and tragedyHomerModern Greek literatureConnectGreek chatHellenism ForumJoin us on FacebookJoin us on TwitterTravel
By using Hellenism.Net you agree to our Privacy Policy, Cookie Policy, and Terms, which we encourage you to review.
AcceptReject Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
